哈登菲尔德镇，伊利诺斯州
黑猫，小妖，帚柄和幽灵
Black cats and goblins and broomsticks and ghosts.
巫婆的南瓜放那烘烤着
Pumpkins of witches are there to roast.
万圣节之夜  1963年
你可能认为，他们在吓我 也许是吧
ou may think, they scare me. You're probably right.
万圣夜里的黑猫和小妖
Black cats and goblins on Halloween night.
不给糖就捣乱！！！
Trick-or-treat!!!
我爸爸妈妈10点后才回来 是吗？
My parents won't be home untill ten.  Are you sure?
没有其他人在吧？
We're all alone, aren't we?
麦克不知去那里了
Michael's around someplace ...
把那东西拿开
Take off that thing.
我们上楼去 好
Let's go upstairs. Ok.
朱迪丝，很晚了，我要走了
Look, Judith, it's very late. I gotta go.
你明天会打电话给我吧？
Will you call me tomorrow?
好，一定 你保证？
Yeah, sure. Promise?
保证
Yeah.
麦克？
Michael?
史密斯森林，伊利诺斯州
10月30日，1978年
你以前有没有处理过这种事？
Ever done anything like this before?
只有在安全限度之内
Only minimum security.
了解了
I see.
入口在右边几百码处
The driveway's a few hundred yards up on the right.
我唯一担心的是他们激动的时候
The only thing that ever bothers me is their jibberish.
会不停的发出各种奇怪的声言
When they start raving on and on ...
不必担心这个
You haven't anything to worry about.
他己经有15年没说过话了
He hasn't spoken a word in 15 years.
有没有要特别注意的事？
Are there any special instructions?
只要清楚我们是在处理什么事就好
Just try to understand what we're dealing with here.
不要掉以轻心
Don't underestimate it.
你不认为我们和他一样也正在期待着这件事？
Don't you think we could refer to 'it' as him?
你要这样说也可以
If you say so.
你的同情心在作祟，大夫
Your compassion's overwhelming, Doctor.
在带他去见法官之前，我还为他做点什么？
What do I give him, when we're taking him in front of the judge?
想法奇怪
Thorazin.
这样根本解决不了问题  我也是这么认为
Barely be able to sit up. That's the idea.
你这次很认真，是不是？
You're serious about that, aren't you?
是的
Yeah.
你是说你实在不希望放他出来  不希望
You mean, you actually never want him to get out. Never ever ...
绝不希望
Never.
那为什么我们还要带他去哈地郡？  因为法律这样规定
Then why we're taking up to Hardy county,if he just gonna ... Because that is the law.
到了
We are.
他们什么时候开始可以四处闲逛的？
Since when do they let them wander around?
到大门去 - 我们不是应该去 - 快走
Pull up to the main gate. Shouldn't we ...  Pull up?
停车
Stop here.
我们不是应该直接去医院的吗？  在这里等着
Shouldn't we go on up to the hospital on ... Wait!
你没事吧？
Are you all right?
你没事吧？- 我没事 - 他跑了
You all right? - Yes, I'm ok. - He's gone. He's gone?
这混蛋跑了
The evil is gone!
我得赶紧
I gotta ...
海德非斯，伊利诺州
万圣节
别忘了拿锁匙去麦尔家
Don't forget to drop the key off the Myers place ...
好的
I won't.
他们会在10点半来看房子把它放在门口被子下面  我会的
They're coming by look at the house at 10:30.Be sure you leave it under the mat ... Promise.
劳莉
Laurie ...
嗨，汤米
Hi Tommy.
今晚你来吗？  同一时间，同一地点
Coming over tonight? Same time, same place.
我们能做杰克灯笼吗？  当然可以
Can we make Jack-O-Lanterns? Sure.
然后看恐怖电影？  对
And watch the monster movies? - Sure.
你会念书给我听吗？
Will you read to me?
能做爆米花吗？  当然，当然，当然
Can we make popcorn? - Sure, sure, sure.
你最好走快点
You better hurry up.
你怎么走这条路上学？  我爸爸叫我走的
How can you walk in the school this way? My dad asked me to.
为什么？
Why?
我要留锁匙
I have to drop off the key.
为什么？
Why?
因为他要卖房子
Because he's gonna sell a house.
为什么？
Why?
因为那是他的工作  哪套房子？
Because that's his job. Where?
麦尔家的房子
The Meyers house.
麦尔家的房子！
The Meyers house!
你最好不要到那里去
You're not supposed to go up there?
不，我要去
Yes, I am.
那是鬼屋
That's a spook house.
看着吧！
Just watch.
郎尼从来不敢进去
Lonnie Elam said never to go up there.
郎尼说那是鬼屋
Lonnie Elam said that's a haunted house.
他说那里面发生过恐怖的事  - 郎尼大概升不到六年级
He said real awful stuff happened there once. - Lonnie Elam probably won't get out of the sixth grade.
我必须走了
I gotta go.
晚上见
I see you tonight.
再见！再见！
Bye.  Bye.
? 多希望能一直陪伴着你 ?
? I wish I had you all alone ... ?
? 只有我们俩人 ?
? Just the two of us ... ?
? 我会拥你入怀 ?
? I would hold you close to me ... ?
? 紧紧拥抱着 ?
? So close to me ... ?
? 只有我们俩人 ?
? Just the two ... ?
这不是我的责任，山姆  噢，不
I'm not responsible, Sam. - Oh, no ...
我跟他们说过他有多危险
I told them how dangerous he was!
你应该设置路障 那小围壁连5岁小孩都阻止不了
You wouldn't have enough two roadblocks and an all-points bulletin wouldn't stop a five-year-old!
但他是你的病人，大夫  如果他很强壮，你应该告诉大家
But he was your patient, Doctor. If precautions weren't strong enough, you should have told somebody.
我跟每个人都说过了！
I told everybody!
但没人听我的话  那我就无能为力了
Nobody listened. - There's nothing else I can do.
你最好回去再打个电话
You can get back in there and get back on the telephone.
告诉他们昨晚什么人逃走了
Tell them exactly who walked out of here last night ...
告诉他们他会逃到哪里  也许只是逃走而己
And tell them exactly where he is going. - Probably going.
我好像在浪费口舌  山姆，他家离这里150里
I'm wasting my time. - Sam, Haddonfield is a hundred and fifty miles away from here.
而且，老实说，他不会开车  他昨晚开得相当好！
Now, now for God's sake, he can't drive a car! - He was doing very well last night!
一定是这里的人教他的
Maybe someone around here gave him lessons.
到了这里这本书就结束了
... and the book ends.
但其实撒母耳要说的是
But what Samuels is really talking about here ...
命运
is fate.
各位知道
You see ...
书里命运跟很多人都有关
fate caught up with several lives here.
不论科林斯采取什么样的行动
No matter what course of action Collins took ...
他都摆脱不了命运的束缚
he was destined to his own fate,
每一天都是命运的安排
his own day of reckoning with himself.
这
The idea ...
就像
is ...
天命
that destiny ...
是非常真实的，具体的东西  我们每个人都得处理好
is a very real, concrete thing that every person has to deal with.
对于命运，撒母耳和卡斯提的观点有什么不同？劳莉？
How does Samuels' view of fate differ from that of Costaine's? Laurie?
叫我吗？
M'am?
回答问题
Answer the question.
卡斯提写到命运某些程度上跟信仰有关
Costaine wrote that fate was somehow related only to religion
而撒母耳认为那只是一种自然物  就像泥土，空气，火和水一样
or where Samuels felt that ... well, fate was like a natural element, like earth, air, fire, and water.
对，撒母耳把命运人格化了
That's right, Samuels definitely personified fate.
撒母耳写到，命运是不可移动的，就像一座山
In Samuels' writing, fate is a moveable like a mountain.
对人来说是无法改变的
It stands, where man passes a way.
命运永远不会改变
Fate never changes.
你，抱南瓜的 你们走开！
You, with pumpkin. Leave me alone!
他会捉到你的！捉到你的，捉到你的
He's gonna get you! - He's gonna get you, he's gonna get you...
恶魔人来了！快走开！
The boogeyman is coming! Leave me alone!
他大概不胆小  你知不知道万圣节是什么节日？
He doesn't believe us. - Don't you know what happens on Halloween?
知道，有糖果吃
Yeah, we get candy.
恶魔人来了！恶魔人来了！恶魔人来了！
The boogey man! - The boogey man, the boogey man, the boogey ...
他己经动身了
He's on his way.
你一定要相信我，警官 他要来哈登菲尔德镇
You gotta believe me officer,he is coming to Haddonfield.
因为我了解他
Because I know him.
我是他的医生 你一定要有所准备
I'm his doctor. You must be ready for him.
不信的话，那就准备棺材吧
If you don't, it's your funeral.
? 我们来自哈登菲尔德镇，我们很自豪 ?
We're from Haddonfield, couldn't be prouder.
? 听不清楚吗，那我们再大声点 ?
Can't hear now, we yell a little louder.
? 我们来自哈登菲尔德镇，我们很自豪 ?
We're from Haddonfield, couldn't be prouder!
? 听不清楚吗，那我们再大声点 ?  噢，看看你
Can't hear now ... continue - Oh, look at you.
快把那些书扔掉 你应该去购物
Get off the books you have. You neeed a shopping cart to get home.
? 嘿，哈登菲尔德镇！?
Heeey Haddonfield! - Yeah, one for me.
这真是赶死人了！早上有三个新的口号要学
You know it's totally insane! We have three new cheers to learn in the morning,
下午有球赛，5点要去做头发，然后8点去跳舞
the game in the afternoon, I have to get my hairdone at five and the dance is at eight.
我的时间都被用光了！
I'll be totally wiped out!
明天再做估计来不及  完全来不及
I don't think get enough to do tommorow. Totally!
跟以前一样，我似乎没事干  这是你自己的错，我不必同情你
As usual, I have nothing to do. - It's your own fault and I don't feel bit sorry for you.
嘿，琳达，劳莉
Hey, Lynda, Laurie!
怎么没等我？
Why didn't you wait for me?
我们等了呀！
We did.
等了15分钟 你根本没出现  胡说！我这不是来了吗？
Fifteen minutes. You totally never showed. - That's not true. Here I am.
怎么了，安妮？你脸上没笑容  我永远不会再笑了
What's wrong, Annie? You're not smiling. - I'm never smiling again.
保罗带我去男更衣室，然后开发神秘领域？  已经被完全开发过了
Paul dragged me into the boys' locker room to tell ... - Exploring uncharted territory?- It's been totally charted.
我们只是聊天
We just talked.
当然，当然
Sure, sure.
他因往窗户扔鸡蛋被人逮住了  然后他父母就不让他出门了
Old jerko got caught throwing eggs and soaping windows. His parents grounded him.
他今晚来不了了
He can't come over tonight.
你今晚不是要去当保姆吗？她当保姆的唯一原因就是为了有个地方  噢，糟了
I thought you were babysitting tonight. The only reason she babysits is to have a place to... Oh shit ...
我已经有地方了
I have a place for that.
我忘了化学课本
I forgot my chemistry book.
有啥关系？我常忘了拿化学课本，数学课本，英语课本
So, who cares? I always forget my chemistry book and my math book and my english book and my ...
有时候法语课本
and let's see my French book and ...
其实没有书也没关系 我根本不需要这些书  我真希望把这些书都丢掉
Who needs books anyway? I don't need books. I always forget all of my books. I mean ...
有没有带书回去根本不要紧
it doesn't really matter if I you got that books or not.
那不是范格拉汉姆吗？
Hey, isn't that the van Graham?
我想不是
I don't think so.
他长得很帅
I think he's cute.
嘿，怪人！
Hey, jerk ...
马路杀手！
Speed kills!
糟了，他不能开玩笑？
Gosh ... Can't he take a joke?
安妮，你总有一天会给我们惹祸的
You know, Annie, some day you gonna get us all into deep trouble.
真的
Totally.
我不喜欢没有幽默感的人
I hate a guy with a car and no sense of humor.
今晚我们还是照旧？
Well, are we still on for tonight?
我不想给你惹麻烦，琳达
I wouldn't want to get you in deep trouble, Lynda.
别这样，安妮
Oh come on, Annie ...
巴伯和我己经计划了一个星期了
Bob and I've been planning on it all week.
好吧！
All right.
华莱士夫妇七点离开家
The Wallaces leave at seven.
我要去道尔家当保姆
I'm babysitting the Doyles.
只隔了三套房子远，我们可以一起玩了  太好了，我有三样选择
It's only three houses down. We can keep each other company. - Ohh, terrific ... I've got three choices.
照看小孩睡觉，和琳达鬼混，还有跟你聊天
Watch the kid sleep, listen to Lynda screw around or talk to you.
我们真
We're so ma ...
这里
Here.
晚上什么时候？
What time at night?
还不知道 我必须把我的小弟弄走然后和和巴伯一起！
I don't know yet. I have to get out of taking my little brother trick- or-treating. - Saving the treats for Bob?
真幽默！
Fun-ny.
再见！  再见！- 再见！
See you. - Bye. - Bye.
安妮，看
Annie, look.
看什么？
Look where?
树林后面
Behind the bush.
我没看到东西  那个刚才开车的，被你吼的那个
I don't see anything. - That guy who drove by so fast, when you yelled at.
他很敏感，是不是？
Subtle, isn't he?
嘿，混蛋！
Hey, creep!
劳莉，亲爱的，他想和你说话
Laurie, dear, he wants to talk to you.
他晚上想和你约会
He wants to take you out tonight.
他刚才站在这里
He was standing right there.
可怜的劳莉
Poor Laurie.
你又失去了一个机会
Scared another one away.
真可悲，你永远无法和男孩约会
It's tragic. You never go out.
你不应该整天帮别人看孩子  别人觉得我聪明
You must have a small fortune stashed from babysitting so much. - Guys think I'm too smart.
我认为你太怪异了 竟然在树丛后看到一个人
I don't. I think you're whacko.Now you're seeing men behind bushes.
温暖的家到了
Well, home sweet home.
待会儿见
See you later.
再见
Bye.
对不起，劳莉  布莱克先生，对不起  我不是有意吓你的
Excuse me, Laurie. - Oh, Mr. Brackett, I'm sorry, Mr. Brackett. - Oh, I didn't mean to scary ya.
对不起
I'm sorry.
今天是万圣节 我想每个人都预期会被吓一吓
You know, it's Halloween. I guess everybody's entitled to a one good scare.
是的，先生
Yes, sir.
很高兴见到你，先生
Nice evening, sir.
不给糖就捣乱 不给糖就捣乱
Trick -o - treat, Trick -o - treat.
小孩子
Oh, kiddo ...
都是在迷信中长大的
thought you grew up from superstition.
哈罗？
Hello?
到底是谁？
Who is this?
哈罗？
Hello?
为什么挂断电话？
Why did you hang up on me?
安妮？
Annie?
刚才是你吗？
Was that you?
是呀！  怎么不说话，吓死我了
Of course. - Why didn't you say anything? You scared me to death.
我嘴里塞满了吃的 你听到吗？
had my mouth full. Couldn't you hear me?
我以为是恐吓电话
I thought it was an obscene phone call.
你听到我只是在吃东西，抱歉  我没听清楚
Now you hear obscene chewing. You're losing it, Laurie. - I've already lost it.
我怀疑
I Doubt that.
听好了，我妈要借车给我，我六点半来接你
Listen, my mother is letting me use her car. I'll pick you up. 6:30.
好，再见！  再见！
Ok, bye. -Bye.
冷静
Just calm down.
真荒谬
This is ridiculous.
快进来
Hurry up.
还有点时间
Just have time.
朱迪丝麦尔 麦尔
Judith Myers. Myers.
第18排第20个
Row 18 ... plot 20.
你可知道这种事经常发生
Hey, you know. You know, every town has something like this happen.
我记得在罗素维尔镇
I remember over in Russellville.
查理包尔 大概在15年前
Old Charly Bowles. About fifteen years ago.
有一天晚上他吃完晚餐
One night he, he finished dinner ...
离开餐桌
And he excused himself from the table ...
到停车库
And he went out to the garage ...
拿了一把斧头
He got himself a hack saw ...
回到房里
And then he went back into the house ...
和他的太太和二个孩子吻别
And he kissed his wife and two children goodbye ...
然后就 到了吗？
And then he proceeded ... - Where are we?
在这里
It's right over here.
麦尔，朱迪丝麦尔，我记得她
Myers, Judith Myers. I remember her.
简直无法相信
Couldn't believe.
这么小的男孩
Such a young boy.
迷路了吗？
Well, you lost?
他们为什么这么做？
Why do they do it?
这些小鬼
Goddamn kids.
在万圣节他们什么事都干得出来
They'll do anything for Halloweens.
这是墓碑  噢，我知道
It was grave, hers. - Oh, I know that.
18，19
18, 19 ...
朱迪丝麦尔的
Judith Myers.
他回来了
He came home.
你还在幻想吗？
You still spooked?
我没有幻想
I wasn't spooked.
你胡说  我没有
Lies. - I wasn't.
我看到有人在李德先生的后院  可能是李德先生本人吧！
Saw somebody standing in Mr. Riddle's back yard. - Probably Mr. Riddle.
他在看着我  李德先生看着你？劳莉，李德先生己经87岁了
He was watching me. - Mr. Riddle was watching you? Laurie, Mr. Riddle is 87.
他还是可以看的呀！
He can still watch.
可能他所能做的只是看看而己
That's probably all he can do.
这南瓜是用来做什么的？  帮汤米带的 他大概要做个杰克灯笼 这能让他忙一阵子
What's the pumkin for? - I brought it for Tommy. I figured carving a Jack-O-Lantern would keep him occupied.
我们应该弄个精彩的女童军游戏
I always said you'd make a fabulous girl scout.
谢谢  老实说，今晚我都要演女童军
Thanks. - And for that matter, I might as well be a girl scout myself tonight.
我计划做爆米花，然后看《痴呆医生》
I plan on making popcorn and watching Doctor Demensia.
六个小时的恐怖电影，小林西肯定会吓一大跳
Six straight hours of horror movies. Little Lindsey Wallace won't know what hit her.
我爸
My dad!
快丢掉
Get rid of this.
劳莉，别咳了，你怎么回事？
Laurie, stop caughing. What's the matter with you?
自然点，他在那里
Just be natural. There he is. Just be natural, Laurie.
安妮，劳莉
Hi, Annie, Laurie...
嗨，爸爸
Hi, Dad.
什么事？ 什么？
What happened?  What? What happened?
有人硬闯进了那间仓库 可能是小孩
Somebody broke into the hardware store. Probably kids.
你把任何事都怪在小孩头上
You blame everything on kids.
他们拿走了一些万圣节面具，一条绳子，还有几把小刀  要不然你认为是谁干的？
What all they took was some Halloween masks, a rope and a couple of knives. Who do you think it was?
很难跟这位偏执的老爸沟通
It's hard growing up with a cynical father.
你要迟到了吧？  什么？
Aren't you gonna be late ... - Huh?
我说你要迟到了  他又在吼了
I said aren't you gonna be late. - He shouts too.
再见！孩子们
Bye girls.
再见！爸爸  再见
Bye dad. - Bye.
警长
Sheriff.
打扰了，我是卢米斯，山姆卢米斯医生
Pardon me, I'm a Loomis. Dr. Sam Loomis.
李布兰提  - 如果可以，我想和你说几句
Lee Brackett. - I, I'd like to have a word with you if I could.
好，稍等几分钟，我得拿那个  这事很重要
Ah, maybe a few minutes. I gotta take that - It's just important.
等十分钟  我在这里等
Ten minutes. - I'll be here.
你怎么了？
What's the matter with you?
我想他知道了，他闻得出来
I think he knew. I'm sure he could smell it.
他闻不出来的  他一定闻出来了
No, he didn't. - He did.
看到他的表情了吗？
See the look on his face?
他一向都是那种表情
He always looks like that.
你明晚舞会穿什么衣服？
What  you gonna wear on dance tommorow night?
我没想到你会问这问题，劳莉
I didn't know you thought about things like that, Laurie.
要知道你可以去请别人  - 不，我不行
You know you could ask somebody. - No, I couldn't.
你当然可以，你只要过去说
Sure you could. All you have to do is go up to somebody and say ...
你想跳舞吗？
You wanna go to the dance?
你可以，我不行
You could do that, I couldn't.
或者你去约迪克帕西特 他会来的
Or you could ask Dick Paxter. He could go out with ya.
那我宁愿约班催莫
I try to get out Ben Tramor.
班催莫？
Ben Tramor?
我就知道！
I knew it!
你一直这样想，对吧，劳莉？
See, you do think about things like that, huh, Laurie?
闭嘴！ 他很帅
Shut up. He is cute.
班催莫！
Ben Tramor.
好
Ok.
再见
Bye.
不给糖就捣乱 不给糖就捣乱
Trick or treat, trick or treat: give me something good to eat.
嗨 - 嗨，安妮，请进  - 今天怎么样？ - 还好，你呢？
Hi. - Hi Annie, come on in. - How are you doing today? - Fine. How are you?
准备几点睡？  九点
What time are you in your bed? I'm being in bed by nine, ok.
玩得开心，亲爱的  - 要乖啊
Have a good night, dear. - Be a good girl.
再见！
Bye bye. - Here.
有人住这里吗？  - 没有，自从1963年发生那事后就没人住了
Anybody lives here? - No, not since 1963 when that happened.
这里的人都认为这是栋凶宅，不干净  - 我也会这么想的
Every kid in Haddonfield thinks this place is haunted. - They may be right.
看！ 什么？
Look. What?
那是什么？
What is that?
一只狗
It's a dog.
还有热度
Still warm.
他一定饿极了
He got hungry.
他已经疯了
Could have been a skunk.
可能是
Could have.
正常人不会这样
A man wouldn't do that ...
他不是正常人
This is not a man.
这就是案发现场
It happened in here.
她当时坐在这里
She was sitting right here ...
他可能从这个窗户看到她
He could have seen her thru this window.
站在草坪上
Standing on the lawn ...
能看到这里
He could have seen in side.
你一定以为我是
You must think of me ...
一个精神不正常的医生
the very sinister doctor.
这是我的医师执照
I do have a permit.
我觉得你好像很害怕
Seems to me you're just plain scared.
是的
Yes.
是的，我
Yeah, I'm a...
我在15年前见他时  我当时认为他己没救
I met him ... fifteen years ago. I was told there was nothing left.
没有知觉，无法沟通  对生命和死亡没有概念
No reason ... nowhere conscience, no understanding in even the most rudimentary sense, of life or death of ...
没有分出善恶的能力
good or evil, right or wrong.
我看到了这个
I met this ...
6岁小孩的那张
six year-old child with his ...
空洞，苍白，没有表情的脸
blank, pale, emotionless face, and ...
和那双来自黑暗的
the blackest eyes ...
魔鬼般的眼睛
the Devil's eyes.
我花了八年的时间想和他沟通
I spent eight years trying to reach him ...
之后七年把他完全拘禁 因为我知道
and then another seven trying to keep him locked up, because I realized that
这个男孩眼睛的后面是无穷无尽的
what was living behind that boy's eyes was purely and simply...
邪恶
... evil.
我们怎么办？
What do we do?
他今晚曾来过
He's been here once tonight ...
我想他会回来
I think he'll come back.
我在这里等他
I'm gonna wait for him.
我认为应该通知广播和电视台  - 不
I still think I should notify the radio and television. - No.
这样人们会恐慌，会到处找他，如此恐怕会打草惊蛇
If you do that, they'll see him on every street corner, they look for him on every house. Just tell your men to keep their ...
还是叫你的人保守机密，严密监视他的出没
mouth shut and their eyes open.
一小时后我再回来看看
I'll check back in an hour.
亚瑟现在哭的很伤心
... oh now, cried Arthur.
“让每个人都加入这场混战！”
'Let no one pass this way without a fight!'
“就这样”骑士大胆
'That's so,' said the knight
而又傲慢的说
in a bold and haughty manner.
我不喜欢那个故事  我以为亚瑟王是你最喜欢的
I don't like that story. - I thought king Arthur was your favorite.
不再是了
Not anymore.
为什么都藏在底下？
Why do you keep them under there?
妈妈不让我留着
Mom doesn't like me to have them.
雷射超人
'Laser Man' ...
中子人，我知道为什么了
'Neutron Man' ... I can understand why.
飞天超人
'Tarantula Man' ...
劳莉
Laurie ...
什么是恶魔人？
what's the Boogeyman?
道尔公馆
Doyle residence.
是我  嗨，安妮，你在做什么？
It's me ... - Hi Annie, what are you doing?
做爆米花
Making popcorn ...
取乐
Having fun ...
你一定也是一样
Never mind, I'm sure you are.
我有一个好消息告诉你
I have big, big news for you ...
你等一下
Hold on a minute.
嗨 李斯特
Hi Lester...
我要被这只恶犬咬得稀巴烂了
I'm about to be ripped apart by the family dog.
林西，快把这只狗从厨房带走
Lindsey ... get this dog out of the kitchen right now.
我恨那只狗  是世界上它唯一不喜欢的人
I hate that dog ... I'm the only person in the world he doesn't like.
是什么大好消息？
So, what is this big, big news?
如果我说你会参加明晚的舞会 你信不信？
What would you say if I told you that you were going to the Homecoming Dance tomorrow night?
我会说你拔错电话号码了
I would probably say you've got the wrong number.
好吧
Well ...
我刚才打电话给班催莫 告诉他你觉得他很有吸引力
I just talked with Ben Tramer and he got real excited when I told him how attracted you were to him.
噢，安妮
Oh, Annie ...
噢，不要，你不会真说了吧
Oh, you didn't. Please tell me you didn't.
你怎么能这样做？
How could you do that?
你怎么打电话告诉他这些？
I mean how you just call him. What do you mean it's easy?
我简直不敢相信
I can't believe this.
我实在不应该把任何事都告诉你
I can't tell you anything.
你一定是在骗我的
Please tell me you didn't.
肯定是骗我的
Oh, you didn't.
好尴尬，我没法见他了  劳莉，恶魔人在外面
Laurie ... - I'm so embarrassed, I couldn't even face him. - Boogeyman is outside.
劳莉，就在那里  等一下
Laurie ... out there. - Hold on.
劳莉，恶魔人在外面，快看！
Laurie, the boogeyman is outside. Look!
汤米，外面没有人
Tommy, there is nobody outside.
去看电视
Go watch TV.
刚才是汤米
It's just Tommy.
噢，安妮
Oh, please, Annie ...
你为什么这样做
You could do that.
很简单，他喜欢你，你也喜欢他  你们需要的是一点推力
Look it's simple. You like him, he likes you. All you need is a little push.
老实说，和他约会只会对你有好处
It won't hurt you to go out with him, for God's sake.
他妈的
Shit!
不不！我把衣服弄湿了  我一会再打给你
No, no, I just made a mess on myself. I gotta call you back.
噢，倒霉！
Oh, yuck!
林西
Lindsey ...
我需要一件衣服
I need a robe.
林西
Lindsey ...
那狗又再叫了 我这样会神经紧张的
Lester's barking again and getting on my nerves again.
没事了
Never mind ...
他一定在约会
I guess he found a hot date.
什么时候做杰克灯笼？  先把电影看完
What about the Jack-O-Lantern? - After the movie.
那我的故事书呢？  做完杰克灯笼再说
What about the rest of my comic books? - After the Jack-O-Lantern.
那恶魔人呢？
What about the boogeyman?
这东西不存在
There is no such thing.
瑞其说他今晚会来抓我
Richie said he was coming after me tonight.
瑞其说什么你都信吗？
Do you believe everything that Richie tells you?
不是
No.
汤米，万圣节的夜晚，大家都想愚弄人
Tommy, Halloween night ... it's when people play tricks on each other.
相信我，瑞其只是想吓吓你
It's all make believe. I think Richie was just trying to scare you.
我看到恶魔人了 他就在外面
I saw the boogeyman. I saw him outside.
外面没有人
There was nobody outside.
有  那他长什么样子？
There was. - What did he look like?
长得像恶魔！
The boogyeman!
这么说没有任何意义
We're not getting anywhere.
好吧
All right.
恶魔人只在万圣节晚上出现，对吧？
The boogyeman can only come out on Halloween night, right?
对
Right.
那好，我整晚都在这里，这样你就不会害怕了吧
Welll, I'm here tonight. I'm not about to let anything happen to you.
你保证？
Promise?
我保证
Promise.
我们现在做杰克灯笼好吗？
Can we make the Jack-O-Lantern now?
走
Let's go.
太棒了！
Hmm, terrific.
哈罗？
Hello?
谁在那里？
Who's there?
保罗，这又是你的恶作剧对吧？
Paul, is this one of your cheap pranks?
也许不是
Guess not.
今晚应该不会有人捉弄我
No tricks for Annie tonight.
林西
Lindsey!
林西，到这边来！
Lindsey, come out here!
林西，我被反锁在洗衣间了！开不了门！
Lindsey, I'm in the laundry room! The door wouldn't open!
大家分头找
Spread out everybody.
我们要弄清楚这个东西长什么样
We gonna try to figure out the shape of this thing.
我的天
Holly cat.
嘿  对了
Hey. - Yeah.
几近完美 怎么了？
Almost perfect. What's wrong?
我们终于找到一个了 我们发现了源头
We finally got one. - We found a plain sourcer.
林西，快去接电话，是保罗打来的
Oh, Lindsey, get the phone, it's Paul.
林西！
Lindsey!
Lindseeey!
不，没有响应 - 博士，这些手指头使从哪来的？
No, no answer. - Doctor, where are those fingers from?
我不清楚，史考特先生  哈罗？
I don't know, Mr. Scott. Hallo?
嗨，林西，我是保罗，安妮在吗？
Hi Lindsey, this is Paul. Is Annie there?
在，她在
Yes, she is.
帮我找她，好不好？
Get her for me, will ya?
她在洗衣服
She's washing her clothes.
告诉她我来过电话，好吗？
Look, just tell her it's me, ok?
好
Ok.
安妮！保罗来电话了
Annie, Paul called!
你怎么挂在那里？  我知道
You locked yourself there. - I know.
拉我一把，我被卡住了
Pull my foot. I'm stuck!
好了，不许跟别人提这件事
Now promise me you won't tell anybody about this.
她刚刚被窗给卡住了，现在回来了
She got stuck in a window. She'll be right here.
哈罗！  嗨，安妮
Hello? Hi Annie.
噢，嗨，保罗  被卡住了，是真的吗？
Oh, hi Paul. Stuck, huh?
好了，不要说了，谁都会  没错，被窗卡住了
All right, cut it out. It can happen to anyone. Sure ... stuck in the widow.
没错，我也看见你卡在很多地方啊
Yeah, but I've seen you stuck in plenty of other positions!
我爸妈出去了
My parents are gone.
太好了，什么时候出去的
Oh that's fabulous. When did they leave?
半小时前  这太好了
About half ago - Oh, utterly fantastic.
你为什么不走路过来？
So why don't you just walk over?
你来接我  现在不行，我在洗衣服
You coming pick me up. - Well, I can't come now. My clothes are in the wash.
那你没穿  住口，混蛋，我穿衣服了，你满脑子净想那些
Oh shut up jerk. Can't, I've got a shirt on. That's all you ever think about.
我觉得你才满脑子想那些  胡说，我想到很多事情
I think that's all you ever think about. - That's not true, I think about lots of things.
为什么我们不停止纸上谈兵去实践一下呢？
Now why don't we not stand here talking about them and get down to doing them?
关好门，锁紧窗户，关掉灯
Lock your doors, bolt your window and turn off the lights.
别离开 一会你将看到奇迹  我好怕
Don't go away ... cause here is a scene ... - I'm scared.
那你为什么要坐在这么暗的地方呢？
Then why are you sitting here with half the lights off?
我不知道  走，去拿你的外套，我们去接保罗
I don't know. - Well, come on get your coat. We're going to pick up Paul.
我不想去
I don't want to.
林西，我以为我们互相了解对方  我想呆在这看电影
Look, Lindsey, I thought we understood each other... - I want to stay here and watch this.
好，我带你去汤米道尔家和他一起看电视，你不好？
Okay, if I can fix it so you can watch TV with Tommy Doyle, would you like that?
好呀！  那跟我走吧
Yes. - Well, come with me.
快点！
Come on! Hurry up.
奇怪的是必须把它清空
That strange that has to short it out.
嗨，汤米
Hi Tommy.
嗨
Hi.
请进，我们正在做杰克灯笼  但是我想看电视
Come on in. We're making a Jack-O-Lantern. - You know I wanna watch TV.
安妮，来这边
Annie, come in here.
现在他们得出了可怕的结论
now the horrifying conclusion to ... the them.
噢，真迷人！
Oh, fancy.
今晚不是属于我的
This has not been my night.
我不小心把牛乳泼在身上，衣服正在洗，我还卡在了窗上  我希望你能打电话给班，告诉他你只是在开玩笑
I spilled butter all over. My cloths are in the wash.I got stuck in a window. I'd like you call Ben Tramer and tell him you're just fooling around.
不行 - 行的，你可以的  不行，他和麦克戈弗雷喝酒，很晚才回来
I can't. - Yes, you can. - No, he went drinking with Mike Godfrey and he won't be back until late.
你明天自己打电话给他
YOU'LL have to call him ... tomorrow.
况且我正要去接保罗
Besides, I'm on my way to pick up Paul.
等一下
Wait a minute.
如果你帮我照看小孩，我会考虑明早打电话给班催莫
If you watch her, I'll CONSIDER talking to Ben Tramer in the morning.
成交
Deal.
我以为保罗被禁足了  没错，这小子想办法溜出来了
I thought Paul was grounded. - He was. Old jerko found a way to sneak out.
我一小时后再打电话给你，好吧？  - 好
Listen, I'll call you in an hour or so, ok? - Yeah.
再见！
Bye.
女童军的性格又表露无遗了
The old girl scout comes through again.
? 今夜，保罗，我什么都给你 ?
? My Paul ... I give you all ?
? 没有锁匙 但我的保罗，请你 ?
? No keys, but pleeease ...  my Paul ?
? 噢，保罗 ?  ? 我不会再晚了 ?
? Oh, Paul ...  I can no longer stall... ?
? 噢，保罗，噢，保罗 ?  ? 我不会再晚了 ?
? Oh Paul. Oh Paul ... I can no longer stall... ?
? 亲爱的保罗 ?
? Dearly Paul ... ?
? 我的保罗 ?
? my Paul ?
注意！
Attention ...
船长和其他人员准备器械
Captain and crew standby reverse polarity.
地点第8检查站，在那里降落
Standard class A security will be maintained upon landing.
直到所有人员出   我们就接收
And until further notice all land in and hold on.
完毕
That is all.
进入重力区域
Artificial gravity are ...
主要出入口封闭
ad lock cut primary coarse.
出入口都封闭了，长官
Primary stature.
林西
Lindsey ...
Lindseyyy ....
你在哪里？
Where are you?
我看到恶魔人了！他在外面！恶魔人在外面！  - 怎么了？
There is the boogeyman! He is outside! Look, there is the boogeyman outside! - What's wrong?
我看到恶魔人！真的 - 汤米，别吵了  在林西家那边！- 你会把林西吓哭的
I saw the boogeyman! I know that - Oh, Tommy stop it! - But at Lindsey's! - You're scaring Lindsey.
他在那里！  汤米，够了！外面没有人！
He's over there! - Tommy, stop it! There is nobody out there!
没有恶魔人，如果你还吵  我就把电视关掉，拉你去睡觉
There's no boogeyman. And if you don't stop all this I'll have to turn off the TV and send you to bed.
没人相信我  我相信你，汤米
Nobody believes me. - I believe you, Tommy.
我才不怕
I'm not afraid.
吹牛
Bull.
我不怕  那就进去吧！
I'm not. - Then go in.
胆小鬼
Chicken.
别发抖，进去吧！郎尼
Go ahead, Lonnie.
进去呀！
Go in!
嘿！
Hey!
嘿，郎尼
Hey, Lonnie ...
你最好别接近那里
Get your ass away from there ...
老天
Jesus.
你还好吧？
Are you all right here?
还好
Yeah.
除了孩子们的嘻斗之外  似乎没发生任何事
Well, nothing's going on except kids playing pranks, trick or treating, partying, getting high.
我觉得你太小提大作了
I have the feeling you're way off on this.
你这样想是不对的  但目前为止尚未证明我是错的
You have the wrong feeling. - You're not doing very much to prove me wrong.
你还需要证明吗？
What more do you need?
当然，要让我整夜都藏在这树丛的后面  靠说这些荒诞的东西还不够
Well, it's going to take more than fancy talk to keep me up all night crawling around these bushes.
我观察他15年了
I, I, I watched him for fifteen years ...
他坐在房间里，呆看着墙壁，不只是看着
sitting in a room, staring at a wall, not seeing the wall ...
甚至要看穿墙壁
looking past the wall
如果你有这耐心
looking at ... THIS NIGHT inhumanly patient.
等一个神密，无声的危险人物
waiting for some secret, silent alarm ...
等待他的出现
to trigger him off.
死亡己逼近你这个小镇，警长
Death has come to your little town, sheriff.
你要么不理不睬，要么帮我阻止他
You can either ignore it or you can help me to stop it.
你又在说怪诞的事
More fancy talk.
大夫，你了解哈登菲尔德镇吗？
Doctor, do you know what Haddonfield is?
家人
Families ...
孩子们，他们都成群结队地在街道上上下下
Children ... all lined up in rows, up and down these streets.
而你却告诉我他们可能会有危险
You're telling me they're lined up for a slaughterhouse.
很有可能
They could be.
好，今晚我和你待在这里
All right, I'll stay with you out tonight ...
就当作你说的不假
just on the chance that you're right.
就算你说的都是事实
And if you are right ...
你也要为他的逃跑负责
damn you for letting him go.
好，我告诉你，我们先进去，好吧？  然后我们谈几句话
So we gonna first, we'll go inside, right? Then we just talk a little.
当安妮把林西支走时，我们就上楼到左边第一个房间 了解了吗？
Then Annie will distract Lindsey, that's when we'll go upstairs to the first bedroom on the left. You got it?
首先我撕掉你的衣服
First I rip your clothes off ...
不要撕我的胸衣，那很贵的，白痴  然后你撕掉我的衣服
Don't rip, my blouse is expensive, idiot. - Then you rip my clothes off...
然后我们把林西的衣服也撕掉  耶！我觉得我全明白了！
then we rip Lyndsey's cloth off. Yeah, I think I got it.
你全明白了
Totally.
巴伯，放我下来
Bob ... put me down.
放我下来，别闹了
Put me down. This is totally silly.
放我下来
Put me down.
怎么这么暗  是呀！
Hey, it's totally dark. - Yeah.
安妮！
Annie!
安妮，我们来了  他们去哪了？
Annie, we're here! - I wonder where they went.
安妮可能带林西出去了
Annie probably took Lindsey out or something.
找找看有没有留字条
Hey, let's look for a note.
别找了
Let's not.
他会抓到你的
He's gonna get you ...
不，他抓不到  嘿，没有谁要抓任何人 不要吓人
No, he's not. - Hey, nobody's getting anybody. Stop scaring each other.
今夜每个人都各得其所
Everybody's having good time tonight.
好，小鬼，下来要玩什么？
All right, guys, what's next?
我们再多做点爆米花吧  不，已经够多了 要不一起把电影看完吧？
Let's make more popcorn. - No, we had enough. Why don't we watch the rest of the movie?
好
Yeah.
好了， 把它放回去
All right, put it back on.
道尔公馆
Doyle house.
嗨，劳莉，怎么样了
Hi Laurie ... what's up?
我今晚才刚刚坐下来
I'm just setting down for the first time tonight.
嘿，安妮在你那里吗？
Hey ... is Annie around?
不在，她现在应该回去了
No, I thought she'd be home by now.
她说要去接保罗  她根本不在这里
She went to pick up Paul. - Well, she's totally not here.
她大概去别地方了
She's probably stopped off some place.
她回去时让她给我打个电话  林西在我这边，我要知道何时叫她去睡觉
Have her call me when she gets home. I've got Lyndsey here and I want to know what time to put her to bed.
好，回见  祝你愉快
Okay. Later. - Have a good time.
我们一定会很愉快的
We definetely will.
再见！
Bye.
林西晚上不会回来了  那太好了
Lindsey is gone for the night. - Hey, now that's wonderful.
妈的！又来了
Oh, shit! Not again.
真受不了，这电话老是响个不停
I can't help it. The phone keeps ringing.
噢，我没法让你保持兴奋，对吗？  还是快接这破电话吧！
Oh, I can't keep you interested, huh? - Just answer that damn phone.
不能接 要是华莱士夫妇打回来的怎么办？
I can't. What if it's the Wallaces?
接了安妮可就麻烦了
We'd get Annie in trouble now.
我们把话筒拿起来
Just take it off the hook.
太棒了！
Fantastic.
太美了  是呀！
Totally. - Yeah.
满足了吗？
Is that all you can say?
是的
Yeah.
去拿瓶酒给我  应该你去拿给我
Go get me a beer. - I thought you were gonna get me one.
快去
Yeaah.
我马上回来
I'll be right back.
不要把衣服穿上
Don't get dressed.
安妮？
Annie?
保罗？
Paul?
林西你这王八蛋
Lynda, you asshole!
好了！琳达
Ok, Lynda.
出来吧！
Come on out.
我的酒呢？
Well, did you get my beer?
可爱，巴伯，你很可爱
Cute, Bob. Real cute.
看到你喜欢的东西了吗？
See anything you like?
怎么了？巴伯，你能脱掉那套衣服吗？
What's the matter? Can I get your ghost, Bob?
好了，别闹了，我的啤酒呢？
All right, all right. Come on, where is my beer?
你回答我好不好？
Ok, ain't answer me?
好，你别回答了
Ok, don't answer me?
你真奇怪！我要打电话给劳莉
Oh, you're weird! - I'm gonna call Laurie.
我要打电话给劳莉  我要知道保罗和安妮去哪里了
Well, I'm gonna call Laurie. I wanna know where Annie and Paul are.
这就不好玩了哦
This is going nowhere.
终于打来了
Finally.
哈罗！
Hello.
哈罗？
Hello?
好了，安妮，上次是在吃东西  这次变成尖叫了？
All right, Annie. First I get your famous chewing, now I get your famous squealing?
安妮，你没事吧？
Annie, you all right?
你是不是又在开玩笑？
Are you fooling around again?
如果又在开玩笑，我会杀了你
I'll kill you if this is a joke.
安妮？
Annie?
好好睡，孩子们
Sleep tight, kids.
保罗？
Paul?
琳达？
Lynda?
安妮？
Annie?
琳达？
Lynda?
巴伯？
Bob?
好了，安妮
All right, Annie ...
好了，你们，玩笑结束了
All right, meatheads. The joke's over.
快出来，安妮
Come on, Annie.
玩够了
It's enough.
已经不好玩了，别闹了
This is most definitely stopping funny. Now cut it out!
你会后悔的
You'll be sorry.
不要
No.
救命！
Help!
快来人呀！
Somebody help me, please!
来人呀！
Somebody help!
噢，上帝，救我！
Oh, God, help me!
快！
Please!
快救我！
Please, help me!
救命！
Heeeelp!
噢，上帝，救我，快点！
Oh, God, help me, please!
哈罗！
Hello!
Helloo!
有人吗？
Hello?
快来救我！
Helloo, help me!
能救救我吗？
Will you please help me?
快！
Please!
你们听到没有？
Can't you hear me?!
天啊！
Oh,God ...
快救我！
Help me, please!
锁匙呢？
The keys!
锁匙！
Oh, the keys!
汤米！
Tommyy!
汤米，是我！
Tommy, it's mee!
汤米！
Tommyy!
谁啊？  汤米，快开门，是我！
Who is it? - Tommy, open up, it's mee!
汤米，快！
Tommy please!
汤米，快点！
Tommy, hurry up!
汤米，求你了！
Tommy please!
快点！汤米，求求你快点！
Hurry up! Tommy please!
汤米快上楼 - 出了什么事，劳莉？  汤米快回楼上去，和林西一起，关好门
Tommy, go upstairs. - What is it, Laurie? - Tommy go back upstairs, grab the Lindsey and lock the door.
我好怕！- 照我说的做！快去！  是恶魔人来了，是吗？- 快点！
I'm scared!- Do what I say! Now! - It's the boogeyman, isn't it? - Hurry!
噢，不要！
Oh, no ...
求求你，不要
Please, stop.
求求你
Please ...
你去哪了？我刚从麦尔家回来  我找到那部车了，他在这里
Where were you? I went to the Meyers house. - I found the car. He is here!
哪里？- 在三个街区之内  你回去在麦尔家附近看看，我在这里找
Where? - He's three blocks down. You go around back off the houses, I'll watch the front.
快呀！
Go on!
汤米！林西
Tommy ... Lyndsey ...
宝贝
Babies ...
我们必须走一段路
We're gonna take a little walk.
是恶魔人吗？
Was it the boogeyman?
- 我好怕  不用怕了
-I'm scared. -There's nothing to be scared of.
真的吗？
Are you sure?
为什么？
How?
我杀了他
I killed him.
你杀不死恶魔人的
You can't kill the boogeyman.
快进去，汤米，把门锁好
Get in there! Come on, Tommy! Now, lock the door!
汤米
Tommy ...
把门打开
Unlock the door.
过来
Come here.
听着
Now just listen to me ...
你们下楼
I want you to go down the stairs ...
把前门锁好
and out the front door.
沿着街去玛肯姬家
And I want you to go down the street to the Mackenzies' house ...
然后叫他们报警
I want you to tell them to call the police.
叫警察来这里
And tell them to send them over here.
劳莉  快去，听到了吗？
Laurie ... - Now, do you understand me?
知道了  快，照我说的做
Yes. - Go. Do as I say.
找人来帮忙！
Get help!
快点！
Come on!
那是恶魔人吗？
Was that the boogeyman?
老实说
As a matter of fact ...
他就是
it was.
月光光心慌慌